

Rudolph van Rensburg

- Potchefstroom, South Africa
- ™ <u>rudolph.vanrensburg@gmail.com</u>
- 076 892 0215
- @ GitHub

Personal Information

Full names: Rudolph Theuns Van Rensburg

Date of birth: 3 September 1996

Gender: Male
Marital status: Single

Nationality: South African

Languages: Afrikaans (Native), English (Fluent)

Profile

Operations Consultant with a background in Agricultural Economics, Risk Management, and IT. I currently specialise in system administration, reporting, and data management, using Python, PowerBI and Excel for analytics. Currently, I am expanding my skills through a full-stack web development course, focusing on web technologies and software development.

Education

BSc Information Technology – Northwest University (2020–2023)
BCom Agricultural Economics & Risk Management – Northwest
University (2017–2020)

Certifications & Courses

Programming Foundations (JavaScript, HTML, CSS) – Duke University (2020)

Full-Stack Web Development - Udemy (Currently busy with course)

Technical Skills

BSc Information Technology

- · Web Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, WordPress.
- Programming: C#, SQL, Java, C++, Python, C.
- Data Analysis: PowerBI, statistical modeling.
- Software Development: Web applications, APIs, system integration.
- · Mathematics: Algebra, Statistics.
- · Project Management.

Technical Skills

BCom Agriculture Economics & Risk Management

- · Economic Analysis.
- · Critical Thinking.
- · Systems Analysis.
- · Monitoring.
- Agricultural Tech: Data-driven farm management, risk mitigation.

Computer skills

- Windows 7, 8, 10 and 11.
- Microsoft Office 2016 & 365: MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, MS Outlook, MS Teams, PowerBi.
- Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome and other Google applications.
- HTML, ASP.NET website development and hosting.
- · Zoom.
- · Internet proficient.

Experience

Khusa Consulting – Operations Consultant (Jan 2024 – Present)

- CRM System Administrator.
- User support for CRM systems.
- · Developed Python scripts for data manipulation and reporting.
- Built PowerBI dashboards for data analysis and business insights.
- · Managed large datasets.
- · Website Redesign.
- · Project-Based Tasks: Ad-hoc projects.
- Reference: Mrs. Kerry-Ann Falls 083 263 6365

Khusa Consulting – Administrative Consultant (2020–2023)

- · Liaise between members and medical schemes.
- Dealing with members or very large client groups.
- Dealing with large medical aids and gap cover providers.
- Reference: Mrs. Rika Calitz 082 309 4917

ALS Construction – Construction Supervisor (June – Aug 2016)

- Supervised general laborers and managed daily material usage.
- Maintained daily reports on materials and project progress.
- Developed organisational and leadership skills, ensuring project deadlines were met.
- Reference: Mr. Ruan Olivier 082 395 0443